I love Patty Lael I love shout out to
Patty Lael honey I went and bought the
Patty Lael pie sweet potato Patty leel
this is the Patty Edition honey this is
the on my own buying this pie it's hard
to get in this Patty what you
see on this with Gorilla Glue oh
it's so pretty look at
that on my
own I did it in this way come on Patty
so let's taste the Patty I want to taste
Patty oh Patty's so moist come on Patty
Patty I'm always hesitant to tell a
black person they remind me of another
black person but he really sounds a lot
like Patrice O'Neal that's James and
since he posted his fabulous review
Walmarts across the country have been
completely sold out of Patty lael's
sweet potato pie I have a hard time
believing anything from Walmart is
edible let alone delicious here we
go
Patty if anybody know Patty the Bell tag
her in the video
Patty I turned into Patty you turn
into Patty after eating
this
[Music]
I
swear pie the greatest pastry chef in
the world could make his best pie and it
would not be as good is the worst
Brownie and don't get me started on
pumpkin pie Jack Lantern guts aren't
food and they're certainly not a dessert
if pumpkin pie or any good it'd be
available year round you know you've
never heard our seasonal milkshake is
chocolate but viral Sensations like
James only come around once every week
or so and since everything he eats gets
wildly popular I figured why not invite
him over for a taste of Tosh everyone
this is James hi everybody how you doing
I heard Patty leel called you shout out
to Patty leel honey what she say she was
just thanking me um for doing the video
and she was just honored she needs to
just open up the checkbook for you you
can't get the pie anywhere in the
country because of your video right that
cuz I'm James right Chanel but do you
know what else you can't get in America
what's that
sroi pastrami no not pastrami it's
stromi it's a Swedish for sour
hering I'm told it's the most putur
smelling food in the
world I'm not used to I don't like that
oh my what the hell is this I know I
I've G I've given you all the
information that I know oh oh my God oh
God
it's and
rock oh my God
[Music]
the oh
through the
night oh my hell no oh say that
oh my
God why the hell does it smell so bad I
can't handar I open did you taste it I'm
you know what it looks
like it looks like potted
meat you want to try
[Applause]
this
oh now I'm sure people at home don't
believe stroming could possibly smell
that bad but I assure you it was worse
that's why I have one more can that I'd
like to pop open in front of my studio
audience
oh
my take a good whip what you get one big
whip can you can you smell it
everywhere come here come here Gary
don't be a
just one big
whip there is that bad no you can't plug
your
nose
what if I do it I don't know if you can
do
[Applause]
it oh that's
Heavenly we'll be right back with more